<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dojo Viz</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dojo Viz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 21:39:12 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EMF Suggestions</title>
      <link>/posts/emf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 21:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emf/</guid>
      <description>Simple EMF Suggestions
Shopping List : Must have stuff to measure and be protected from EMF. 🔗Protection Tips : Some stuff do not worth the loss of health. There will be some simple tips and tricks to be protected from daily EMF exposure. 🔗 Shopping List 🔗  https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B078T2R64C TriField EMF Meter Model TF2 One of the best EMF meter for non professional work. It has standard, weighted and RF settings and battery lasts really long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Network</title>
      <link>/posts/homenetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 20:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/homenetwork/</guid>
      <description>My personal suggestions and usage for home network. 🔗Insurgo laptop with Qubes OS
 Trading: Has only firefox installed with metamask. All important links are already bookmarked. It goes through Tor + VPN (dedicated IP) so that I don&amp;rsquo;t always see captcha errors. Vault: All my licenses, passwords, and everything is stored here, with no internet connection. Even if this is compromised, there is no problem as I use 2fa for all critical accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic settings for Firefox</title>
      <link>/posts/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 03:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/setup/</guid>
      <description>Settings for freshly installed Firefox. 🔗In the firefox: 🔗In settings:
Disable *Enable Picture-in-picture video controls* Set home pages to black page Disable all Home Content Set your default search engine to DuckDuckGo and disable the links of others. Disable *Provide search suggestions* Set Enhanced Tracking Protection to *strict* Enable *Delete cookies and site data when Firefox* Disable Ask to save logins and password for websites Disable keeping history Block permissions for location, camera, microphone and notifications Disable Firefox Data Collection and Usa Enable HTTPS-Only Mode in all windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>web3 Security Audit</title>
      <link>/posts/sec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 22:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sec/</guid>
      <description>the web3 Security Audit
Extreme Measure : Separating everything with already hardened laptops. You can DIY your laptop like that, but it needs tons of time and research, so if you like this stuff, it is always good to know but not recommended for non-tech people. 🔗General Usage Tips : General usage suggestions applied to all computers and operating systems. BUT I will not suggest using Windows. Linux &amp;gt; MacOS &amp;gt; Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
