<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dojo Viz</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dojo Viz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 01:39:12 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BvB Setup</title>
      <link>/posts/bvb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 01:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bvb/</guid>
      <description>BvB PvP Guide
I know you never expected that, me neither. However I am playing diablo since the day Diablo 3 released. And always have been a fan of barbarian, especially WW barb.
so I will give some information about how to utilize a great BvB Barbarian PvP character with extra info about other setups. This will be a short one since the other big part is the experince.
First things first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coldwallet tips</title>
      <link>/posts/coldwallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coldwallet/</guid>
      <description>Cold Wallet Tips &amp;amp; Suggestions
Suggestions: As everyone has become accustomed to these days, cryptocurrency remains one of the safest methods for storing and spending money. As the market heats up, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to be prepared for the next bull run. However, with the increasing money and activity, there will inevitably be bad actors looking to exploit vulnerabilities.
I witnessed firsthand when my friend, who was a developer for Harmony, was hacked for around $800k.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GrapheneOS App Suggestions</title>
      <link>/posts/graphene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 03:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/graphene/</guid>
      <description>GrapheneOS app suggestions
GrapheneOS is an opensource operating system for Pixel phones aimed to be the most secure and private OS for mobile phones.
It has some flaws as it sandboxes everything even Google Services. But nothing is unusable at least for my usage. Only thing I encounder, some notifications might delay like whatsapp.
Here you can find some Tips&amp;amp;Tricks and App suggestions.
Tips &amp;amp; Tricks
 Use work profile for banking apps, just to add an extra layer of security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Audit</title>
      <link>/posts/homeaudit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 20:26:29 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/homeaudit/</guid>
      <description>Here are some self audit stuff you can do around your home easily.
Summary: 🔗 Avoid chemicals Avoid radiation  Long version:
Wifi - EMF 🔗 Use shielded ethernet cable like this one Once you do this, it is best to turn off Wi-Fi in your modem. Have proper grounding, if you do not have call a good electirician. Keyboard/Mouse: Best to use and old vintage ball wired mouse. For keyboard have a nice simple wired keyboard few inches away from your laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMF Suggestions</title>
      <link>/posts/emf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 21:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emf/</guid>
      <description>Simple EMF Suggestions
Shopping List : Must have stuff to measure and be protected from EMF. 🔗Protection Tips : Some stuff do not worth the loss of health. There will be some simple tips and tricks to be protected from daily EMF exposure. 🔗 Shopping List 🔗  https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B078T2R64C TriField EMF Meter Model TF2 One of the best EMF meter for non professional work. It has standard, weighted and RF settings and battery lasts really long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Network</title>
      <link>/posts/homenetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 20:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/homenetwork/</guid>
      <description>My personal suggestions and usage for home network. 🔗Insurgo laptop with Qubes OS
 Trading: Has only firefox installed with metamask. All important links are already bookmarked. It goes through Tor + VPN (dedicated IP) so that I don&amp;rsquo;t always see captcha errors. Vault: All my licenses, passwords, and everything is stored here, with no internet connection. Even if this is compromised, there is no problem as I use 2fa for all critical accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic settings for Firefox</title>
      <link>/posts/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 03:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/setup/</guid>
      <description>Settings for freshly installed Firefox. 🔗In the firefox: 🔗In settings:
Disable *Enable Picture-in-picture video controls* Set home pages to black page Disable all Home Content Set your default search engine to DuckDuckGo and disable the links of others. Disable *Provide search suggestions* Set Enhanced Tracking Protection to *strict* Enable *Delete cookies and site data when Firefox* Disable Ask to save logins and password for websites Disable keeping history Block permissions for location, camera, microphone and notifications Disable Firefox Data Collection and Usa Enable HTTPS-Only Mode in all windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>web3 Security Audit</title>
      <link>/posts/sec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 22:39:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sec/</guid>
      <description>the web3 Security Audit
Extreme Measure : Separating everything with already hardened laptops. You can DIY your laptop like that, but it needs tons of time and research, so if you like this stuff, it is always good to know but not recommended for non-tech people. 🔗General Usage Tips : General usage suggestions applied to all computers and operating systems. BUT I will not suggest using Windows. Linux &amp;gt; MacOS &amp;gt; Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
